{
    "id": "46826e75fb564a1db1cb8f38fcfca67b",
    "title": "Although, But, So And Because",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "....................................... I like him I don't want to spend every evening with him.",
            "description": "We use although to connect two contrasting ideas. It is a subordinating conjunction and usually goes at the beginning of the clause. ",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "But",
                "Because"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "238b971a21d946c5b8e9b4beaf789482"
        },
        {
            "question": "She liked him ......................................... she did not want to marry him.",
            "description": "But is a coordinating conjunction. It has more or less the same meaning as although but it is used to connect two clauses of equal rank. ",
            "answers": [
                "although",
                "but",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bd7c44b3462a4baaa53f8cee5cbf4361"
        },
        {
            "question": ".......................................... John had more years of experience than Peter, he did not get the promotion.",
            "description": "We use although to connect two contrasting ideas. It is a subordinating conjunction and usually goes at the beginning of the clause. ",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "But",
                "Because"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2e3fd2371903425789821467da3847ec"
        },
        {
            "question": "She wanted to go on holiday ........................................ she was short of money.",
            "description": "But is a coordinating conjunction. It has more or less the same meaning as although but it is used to connect two clauses of equal rank. ",
            "answers": [
                "although",
                "but",
                "because"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2ad955357b124534bbf9af6faf6dfbf7"
        },
        {
            "question": "................................................ few people participated in the program, it was a commercial success.",
            "description": "We use although to connect two contrasting ideas. It is a subordinating conjunction and usually goes at the beginning of the clause. ",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "But",
                "Because"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "37e2650f286c464e8decb5ad960a2910"
        },
        {
            "question": "I did not understand a thing .......................................... I said nothing.",
            "description": "But is a coordinating conjunction. It has more or less the same meaning as although but it is used to connect two clauses of equal rank. ",
            "answers": [
                "although",
                "but",
                "because"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "152a8ac5098f43c09280e7f89d89ed70"
        },
        {
            "question": ".......................................... I find it relaxing, I often go to movies.",
            "description": "We use because to introduce the reason for something. ",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "But",
                "Because"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5dc425b8b49c490c8c192cbac64690cb"
        },
        {
            "question": "............................................... she was short of money she could not buy the ticket.",
            "description": "We use because to introduce the reason for something. ",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "Because",
                "So"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "12572dc8127b4288bb5108b0b715ae38"
        },
        {
            "question": ".................................................... I love him, I always support him.",
            "description": "We use because to introduce the reason for something. ",
            "answers": [
                "Because",
                "Although",
                "But"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "43a06c2ec18243de92bf839f032f843f"
        },
        {
            "question": "The last bus had gone .............................................. we had to walk home.",
            "description": "We use so to introduce the result or effect of the action mentioned in the previous clause. ",
            "answers": [
                "although",
                "because",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0afb4ebddfa042f385747c72549d4f2f"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was upset ................................................ he said nothing.",
            "description": "We use so to introduce the result or effect of the action mentioned in the previous clause. ",
            "answers": [
                "although",
                "because",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "471497b28c6242e2a42f00bd013d2a86"
        },
        {
            "question": "................................................... he is a foreigner he cannot find a job easily.",
            "description": "We use because to introduce the reason for something. ",
            "answers": [
                "Because",
                "Although",
                "So"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dd0a8f9fc43a4191a4904870338bca0d"
        }
    ]
}